Ok, here we are, right?
What you are going to need to know, I've been saying it all along.
Use a wall or a person to help you learn how to ride a unicycle, right.
So, we found a wall right here.
We have not started rolling yet.
We have just gotten up to this wall, we got up on our unicycle using our dominate foot at six-o-clock.
Do your walking exercises here.
Hundred right.
Hundred left.
Then a hundred right like this.
Then a hundred left, like this.
This going to get you more familiar with the unicycle like I was saying before.
Also in this next step, you are going to use the handle.
The handle is right here under your seat.
You're going to hold onto the handle, get yourself adjusted.
Because a unicycle is going to move every which way.
It?s going to go forward.
It?s going to go backwards.
Its going to go side to side.
There's so much balance needed to do this.
That your going to really want to get comfortable before you actually get going on your unicycle.
So, sit down on your seat.
Do your walks.
After while start walking with your pedals at three and nine-o-clock.
This is going to help you get a little more uncomfortable with it.
So once you've learned how to do the bottom rocks, learn to do the side rocks.
And a good one to do is to stand up on it, and use your handle to get really familiar with the top of the unicycle here.